<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="questions_array">
        <item name="q_1">How do you find the missing number in a given integer array of 1 to 100?</item>
        <item name="q_2">How do you find multiple missing numbers in a given integer array of 1 to 100?</item>
        <item name="q_3">How do you find the duplicate numbers of a given integer array using loops?</item>
        <item name="q_4">How do you find the duplicate numbers of a given integer array using a set?</item>
        <item name="q_5">How do you find the number of times a duplicate number appears in an array?</item>
        <item name="q_6">How are duplicates removed from a given array in Java?</item>
        <item name="q_7">How do you find the largest and smallest number in an unsorted integer array?</item>
        <item name="q_8">How do you find all pairs of an integer array whose sum is equal to a given number using loops?</item>
        <item name="q_9">How do you find all pairs of an integer array whose sum is equal to a given number using a set?</item>
        <item name="q_10">How do you reverse an array?</item>
        <item name="q_11">Rotate a square matrix by 90 degrees clockwise</item>
        <item name="q_12">Rotate a square matrix by 90 degrees counterclockwise</item>
        <item name="q_13">Modify a matrix so that a 0 in any row or column will create a new matrix where all the values in the same column and row will show 0</item>
        <item name="q_14">How do you find the length of a singly linked list?</item>
        <item name="q_15">How do you check if a given linked list contains a cycle?</item>
        <item name="q_16">How are duplicate nodes removed in an unsorted linked list?</item>
        <item name="q_17">How do you reverse a linked list?</item>
        <item name="q_18">Find middle element of a linked list and remove it</item>
        <item name="q_19">Return the kth to last node in a linked list</item>
        <item name="q_20">Find the sum of two linked lists whose nodes are added together</item>
        <item name="q_21">How do you determine if a linked list is a palindrome</item>
        <item name="q_22">Create a new linked list from a partition around a specified element</item>
        <item name="q_23">Find the intersection of two linked lists</item>
        <item name="q_24">How to determine if all characters in a string are unique?</item>
        <item name="q_25">How to determine if a string Is a palindrome?</item>
        <item name="q_26">Take a given string and encode it as if it was entered into a url</item>
        <item name="q_27">How do you compress a string that has multiple consecutive characters?</item>
        <item name="q_28">Rotate a substring around a particular character</item>
        <item name="q_29">How do you determine if a string permutation is a palindrome?</item>
        <item name="q_30">Determine if two strings are one edit away from each other</item>
        <item name="q_31">Create the smallest minimal tree from a sorted array</item>
        <item name="q_32">Create a linked list of depths</item>
        <item name="q_33">Check if a given tree is balanced</item>
        <item name="q_34">Validate if a given tree is a binary search tree (BST)</item>
        <item name="q_35">In-order successor</item>
        <item name="q_36">Check if a given tree is a subtree or a larger tree</item>
        <item name="q_37">Paths with sum</item>
        <item name="q_38">First common ancestor</item>
        <item name="q_39">Starting from 1 write an algorithm that replaces each number divisible by 3 with Fizz and each number divisible by 5 with Buzz all the way to 100</item>
        <item name="q_40">Stock Prices</item>
        <item name="q_41">Write an algorithm to print the fibonacci sequence</item>
        <item name="q_42">Convex Polygon</item>
        <item name="q_43">Declare an array</item>
        <item name="q_44">Print array</item>
        <item name="q_45">Create ArrayList from an array</item>
        <item name="q_46">Check if an array contains a certain value</item>
        <item name="q_47">Concatenate two arrays</item>
        <item name="q_48">Convert an ArrayList to an array</item>
        <item name="q_49">Convert an array to a Set</item>
        <item name="q_50">Get the first and last element</item>
        <item name="q_51">Get random element</item>
        <item name="q_52">Append a new item to an array</item>
        <item name="q_53">Compare two arrays</item>
        <item name="q_54">Check if an array is empty</item>
        <item name="q_55">Filter values in an array</item>
        <item name="q_56">Find the sum and the average</item>
        <item name="q_57">Sort an array of strings and numbers</item>
        <item name="q_58">Find the index of an element</item>
        <item name="q_59">Remove a specific element</item>
        <item name="q_60">Insert at a specific index</item>
        <item name="q_61">Find common elements between two arrays</item>
        <item name="q_62">Find 2nd largest element</item>
        <item name="q_63">Find 2nd smallest element</item>
        <item name="q_64">Add two matrices of the same size</item>
        <item name="q_65">Move all 0s to the end of an array</item>
        <item name="q_66">Find the number of even and odd integers</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>